所以，现在我们有一个简单的服务，不是么？
So, now, we have a simple service. Wasn't that easy?
但是他仍然不能激活他自己。幸运的是，这有一个专门
But it still doesn't wake itself up. Fortunately, there's a system
为他准备的系统服务。这刚好是引入AlarmManager的好机会。
service for that. This is a good opportunity to introduce
AlarmManager允许你通知系统，让系统知道你想用它
the AlarmManager. The AlarmManager allows you to tell the system that
来激活一个你应用程序的组件，
you want it to wake a component of your application
并且在后台做一些处理。
up after a period of time and do some processing in
你甚至可以偶尔用它来激活
the background. You can even have it wake up your
你的应用程序。但是，我们是怎么在后台激活的呢？
application periodically but, what do we wake up in the background?
这将是一个Android组件，在他被叫做
That would be an Android component we haven't
Broadcast Receiver之前，我们是从来都没有见过的。Broadcast Receiver
seen before called a Broadcast Receiver. A Broadcast Receiver
是一个特殊类，它经常被用来
is a special class, that is used to
接收来自其他应用程序的intent broadcast。一个
receive intent broadcast often from other applications. Typically a
broadcast receiver将会象征性的为这些broadcaast记录一个intent filter
broadcast receiver will register an intent filter for
这也是一种应用程序监听警报的一种方法。
these broadcasts. It's also one way the application will
所以让我们添加一些alarm stuff吧。
listen in on alarms. So let's add some alarm
首先，我们要添加一个Broadcast Receiver
stuff. First, I'm going to add a Broadcast Receiver
作为Sunshine服务的一个静态内部类。
as a static inner class of Sunshine Service.
但他成为一个Android组件之后，我们要在
Since this is an Android component, I'll register
菜单里记录这个Broadcast Receiver。注意
this Broadcast Receiver in the manifest. Note the
在这种方式下静态内部类是以符号出现的。好的，
way a static inner class is notated. Okay, I've
我已经把Broadcast Receiver的核心部分给你了，
given you the bones of a broadcast receiver
这样就可以控制一个alarm了，但是现在
that can handle an alarm, but now it's
轮到你了。你可以从已经明确的意图中新建一个PendingIntent
your turn. You can create a PendingIntent from
让alarm manager激活你的broadcast receiver。
an explicit intent to have the alarm manager activate
我建议你先随便给设置个短警报，比方说5秒，
your broadcast receiver. I recommend setting the alarm to something absurdly
这样你就可以很轻松地测试他的工作状态了。
short, like five seconds, so you can easily test that it's working.